http://www.solvar.ie/more_from_solvar/data-privacy.html

×
Quick Order
Please open the website on a larger device to use the quick order functionality.
Search Product Code
(or) Keyword(s)
Add to Cart
By continuing to use this site you consent to the use of cookies in accordance with our
Shop
CollectionsAll CollectionsBroochesHistory of IrelandAll History of IrelandSterling Silver14K GoldBirthstone JewelleryAll Birthstone JewelleryBirthstone RingsBirthstone NecklacesConnemara MarbleAll Connemara MarbleBangles & BraceletsEarringsPendantsRingsKidsAll KidsRingsEarringsPendantsWristwearFirst CommunionGoldAll Gold9K Gold10K Gold14K Gold14K White GoldSterling SilverAll Sterling SilverRingsEarringsPendantsBeadsBraceletsBanglesGold & SilverCeltic SymbolsAll Celtic SymbolsThe CladdaghAll The CladdaghCladdagh RingsEarringsPendantsBangles and BraceletsCharms and BeadsThe Trinity KnotAll The Trinity KnotRingsPendantsEarringsBracelets & BanglesBeads & CharmsThe ShamrockAll The ShamrockRingsPendantsEarringsBeads & CharmsThe Celtic CrossAll The Celtic CrossPendantsCharmsEarringsFor MenCeltic DesignAll Celtic DesignRingsEarringsPendantsBangles & BraceletsBeads & CharmsFor MenThe Tree of LifeAll The Tree of LifeBeads & CharmsBracelets & BanglesEarringsPendantsThe HarpAll The HarpCharmsPendantsThe St Brigids CrossAll The St Brigids CrossCharmsPendantsGift IdeasAll Gift IdeasGifts for HerAll Gifts for HerBanglesEarringsPendantsRingsGifts for HimAll Gifts for HimBraceletsCufflinksPendantsRingsGifts for KidsAll Gifts for KidsBanglesEarringsPendantsRingsRingsAll RingsSterling SilverAll Sterling SilverCelticCladdaghShamrockTrinity KnotGold & Silver9K GoldAll 9K GoldCladdaghTrinity Knot10K Gold14K GoldAll 14K GoldCladdaghTrinity Knot14K White GoldAll 14K White GoldCladdaghTrinity KnotPendantsAll PendantsSterling SilverAll Sterling SilverCeltic CrossCeltic DesignCladdaghHarpShamrockSt Brigids CrossTree of LifeTrinity KnotGold & Silver9K GoldAll 9K GoldCeltic CrossCeltic DesignCladdaghShamrockTrinity Knot10K GoldAll 10K GoldCeltic CrossCladdaghShamrockTree of LifeTrinity Knot14K GoldAll 14K GoldCeltic CrossCeltic DesignCladdaghHarpShamrockSt Brigids CrossTree of LifeTrinity Knot14K White GoldAll 14K White GoldCeltic CrossCladdaghShamrockTrinity KnotEarringsAll EarringsSterling SilverAll Sterling SilverCelticCladdaghCrossShamrockTree of LifeTrinity KnotSterling Silver & Gold9K GoldAll 9K GoldCladdaghShamrockTrinity Knot10K GoldAll 10K GoldCelticCladdaghShamrockTrinity Knot14K GoldAll 14K GoldCeltic DesignCladdaghShamrockTree of LifeTrinity Knot14K White GoldAll 14K White GoldCladdaghShamrockTrinity KnotWristwearAll WristwearBraceletsAll BraceletsSterling SilverSterling Silver & GoldBanglesAll BanglesSterling SilverCuff BanglesSilver BeadsCharmsAll Charms10K Gold14K Gold14K White Gold9K GoldFor MenAll For MenRingsAll RingsCeltic DesignCladdaghPendantsAll PendantsCeltic CrossCeltic DesignBraceletsCufflinks
Contact Us
Blog & News
Behind the scenes at our photoshoot
Choosing a Claddagh ring
Claddagh Birthstone Collection
First Communion Gifts
History of Ireland Symbols
How to wear your Claddagh Ring
Symbols of Ireland
* VIEW OUR ORDER DEADLINES FOR GUARANTEED CHRISTMAS DELIVERY *
close
Shop
Collections
Brooches
History of Ireland
Birthstone Jewellery
Connemara Marble
Kids
Close
Solvar Limited Privacy PolicyThis Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from www.solvar.ie PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECTWhen you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information.”We collect Device Information using the following technologies    - “Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org.    - “Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.    - “Web beacons,” “tags,” and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site.Additionally when you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through the Site, we collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, shipping address, payment information (including credit card numbers, email address, and phone number.  We refer to this information as “Order Information.”When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information and Order Information.HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?We use the Order Information that we collect generally to fulfil any orders placed through the Site (including processing your payment information, arranging for shipping, and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations).  Additionally, we use this Order Information to:Communicate with you;Screen our orders for potential risk or fraud; andWhen in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services.We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimise our Site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Site, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns)SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATIONWe share your Personal Information with third parties to help us use your Personal Information, as described above.  For example, we use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site--you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here:  https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/.  You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here:  https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.As described above, we may use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you.  For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work.Additionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at:  http://optout.aboutads.info/.DO NOT TRACKPlease note that we do not alter our Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.YOUR RIGHTSIf you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information belowAdditionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above.  Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States.DATA RETENTIONWhen you place an order through the Site, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.CHANGESWe may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.CONTACT USFor more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by e-mail at info@solvar.ie or by mail using the details provided below:Block 2, Westpoint Business Court, John F Kennedy Drive, Dublin, L, D12 E138, Ireland
Share this
EUR
GBP
USD
CAD
ABOUT SOLVAR
About Solvar
History & Heritage
